Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XXIV. LOCAL LODGES
  - Sub-Series 235-449. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 449, Sunshine Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1928-1961 (Box 128, Folder 19)
      1928-Dec. 31, 1961.
  - Sub-Series 235-450. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 450, Signal Mountain Lodge, Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1922-1961 (Box 128, Folder 20)
      1922-Dec. 31, 1961.
  - Sub-Series 235-451. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 451, West Detroit Lodge, Detroit, Michigan, 1921-1928 (Box 128, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 235-452. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 452, Wheeling and Lake Erie (W. & L. E.) General Office Lodge, Cleveland, Ohio, 1921-1951 (Box 128, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 235-456. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 456, Iron Ore Handlers Lodge, Escanaba, Michigan, 1922-1938 (Box 128, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 235-457. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 457, Ft. Wayne Lodge, Ft. Wayne, Indiana, 1948-1951 (Box 128, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 235-458. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 458, Danville, Kentucky, 1925-1956 (Box 128, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 235-460. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 460, Memorial Lodge, Springfield, Massachusetts, 1939-1963 (Box 128, Folder 26)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 336 effective Jan. 1, 1963
  - Sub-Series 235-464. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 464, Elkhart Lodge, Elkhart, Indiana, 1922-1961 (Box 128, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 235-465. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 465, Everett Lodge, Everett, Washington, 1922-1946 (Box 128, Folder 28)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 1380 effective Jan. 1, 1946
  - Sub-Series 235-467. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 467, Hickory Lodge, Hickory, North Carolina, 1923-1961 (Box 128, Folder 29)
      Consolidated with Lodges 313 and 445 effective Oct. 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-469. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 469, Durham Lodge, Durham, North Carolina, 1929-1961 (Box 128, Folder 30)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 220 effective March 31, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-471. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 471, Athens, Georgia, 1922-1930 (Box 128, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 235-472. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 472, Prosperity Lodge, Huntington, West Virginia, 1935-1958 (Box 128, Folder 32)
      1935-Dec. 31, 1958.
    - Lodge No. 472, Zanesville Lodge, Zanesville, Ohio, 1928-1932 (Box 128, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 235-474. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 474, Canada Malting Lodge, Ft. William, Ontario, Canada, 1947-1952 (Box 128, Folder 33)
      Suspended effective Dec. 1, 1952
    - Lodge No. 474, Victory Lodge, Moose Jaw, Saskatchewan, Canada, 1943-1946 (Box 128, Folder 33)
      Disbanded effective Sept. 5, 1947
    - Lodge No. 474, New York District Lodge, Jamaica, New York, 1935 (Box 128, Folder 33)
      May 1935-June 1935.
    - Lodge No. 474, St. Louis, Missouri, 1940 (Box 128, Folder 33)
      1940 May 22. Consolidated with Lodge No. 280 effective Oct. 14, 1942
    - Lodge No. 474, Akron Lodge, Akron, Ohio, 1921-1923 (Box 128, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 235-475. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 475, Grand Trunk Western Lodge, Muskagon, Michigan, 1944-1962 (Box 129, Folder 1)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 950 effective Jan. 1, 1962
    - Lodge No. 475, Grand Ronde Lodge, LaGrande, Oregon, 1923-1924 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 235-476. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 476, Union Station Lodge, Texarkana, Texas, 1959-1969 (Box 129, Folder 2)
      Jan. 1, 1959-69. Consolidated with Lodge No. 839 effective July 1, 1969
    - Lodge No. 476, Union Station Lodge, Texarkana, Texas, 1935-1958 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Lodge No. 476, Hermitage Lodge, Nashville, Tennessee, 1921-1924 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 235-477. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 477, Fort Garry Lodge, Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada, 1935-1960 (Box 129, Folder 5)
      Consolidated with Lodges 2066 and 2072 effective July 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-480. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 480, Seaboard Lodge, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1922-1950 (Box 129, Folder 6)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 876 effective Oct. 1, 1950
  - Sub-Series 235-481. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 481, Erie Lodge, Jamestown, New York, 1935-1938 (Box 129, Folder 7)
      Suspended effective July 15, 1938
  - Sub-Series 235-485. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 485, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1935-1937 (Box 129, Folder 8)
      Suspended Aug. 17, 1937
  - Sub-Series 235-486. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 486, Electric City Lodge, Scranton, Pennsylvania, 1922-1962 (Box 129, Folder 9)
      1922-Dec. 31, 1962. Changed from Lodge No. 486, Hornell Accounting Bureau Lodge, Hornell, New York effective Nov. 28, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-490. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 490, Erie Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1943-1958 (Box 129, Folder 10)
      1943-Dec. 31, 1958.
    - Lodge No. 490, Mt. Vernon Lodge, Alexandria, Virginia, 1921-1927 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 235-491. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 491, Premier Lodge, Buffalo, New York, 1939-1963 (Box 129, Folder 11)
      1939-Dec. 31, 1963.
  - Sub-Series 235-492. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 492, Danville Lodge, Danville, Virginia, 1946-1969 (Box 129, Folder 12)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 220 effective April 1, 1969
  - Sub-Series 235-493. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 493, Detroit, Toledo and Ironton (D. T. & I.) Lodge, Dearborn, Michigan, 1939-1959 (Box 129, Folder 13)
      1939-Dec. 31, 1959.
    - Lodge No. 493, Capital City Lodge, Springfield, Illinois, 1935-1937 (Box 129, Folder 13)
    - Lodge No. 493, Toronto Lodge, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1921-1922 (Box 129, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 235-497. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 497, Hornell Accounting Bureau, Lodge, Hornell, New York, 1923-1951 (Box 129, Folder 14)
      Changed from "Maple City" Lodge
  - Sub-Series 235-499. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 499, Hamilton, Ontario, Canada, 1948-1950 (Box 129, Folder 15)
      Disbanded June 12, 1950
    - Lodge No. 499, Black Diamond Lodge, Peach Creek, West Virginia, 1945 (Box 129, Folder 15)
      Dec. 13, 1945.
    - Lodge No. 499, Iron Ore Handlers Lodge, Marquette, Michigan, 1921 (Box 129, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 235-501. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 501, James River Lodge, Lynchburg, Virginia, 1938-1960 (Box 129, Folder 16)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 221 effective July 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-502. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 502, Newark Lodge, Newark, Ohio, 1926-1958 (Box 129, Folder 17)
      1926-Dec. 31, 1958.
  - Sub-Series 235-503. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 503, Blue Grass Lodge, Danville, Kentucky, 1929-1966 (Box 129, Folder 18)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 1083 effective July 1, 1966
  - Sub-Series 235-504. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 504, Pacific Fruit Express General Office Lodge, San Francisco, California, 1930-1962 (Box 129, Folder 19)
      1930-Dec. 31, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 235-506. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 506, Rivanna Lodge, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1945-1967 (Box 129, Folder 20)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 508 effective July 1, 1967
  - Sub-Series 235-507. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 507, Bluff City Lodge, Memphis, Tennessee, 1921-1960 (Box 129, Folder 21)
      1921-Dec. 31, 1960.
  - Sub-Series 235-511. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 511, Royal Blue Lodge, Lansdowne, Maryland, 1921-1961 (Box 129, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 235-512. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 512, Dupo Lodge, Dupo, Illinois, 1921-1960 (Box 129, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 235-513. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 513, Council Bluffs Lodge, Council Bluffs, Iowa, 1950-1961 (Box 129, Folder 24)
      1950-Dec. 31, 1961.
    - Lodge No. 513, Council Bluffs Lodge, Council Bluffs, Iowa, 1921-1949 (Box 129, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 235-514. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 514, Brigham Lodge, Baltimore, Maryland, 1921-1961 (Box 129, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 235-515. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 515, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1922 (Box 129, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 235-518. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 518, William Penn Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1921-1959 (Box 129, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 235-519. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 519, Wheeling Lodge, Wheeling, West Virginia, 1921-1956 (Box 129, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 235-520. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 520, Terminal Lodge, Hoboken, New Jersey, 1939-1966 (Box 129, Folder 30)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 6 effective Oct. 1, 1965
  - Sub-Series 235-521. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 521, St. Clair Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1922-1962 (Box 129, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 235-524. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 524, Mound City Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1921-1953 (Box 129, Folder 32)
      1921-Dec. 31, 1953.
  - Sub-Series 235-525. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 525, Lakewood Lodge, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1946-1949 (Box 130, Folder 1)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 1142 effective March 1, 1955
    - Lodge No. 525, Westmary Lodge, Baltimore, Maryland, 1945-1946 (Box 130, Folder 1)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 385 effective Jan. 1, 1946
    - Lodge No. 525, Rainbow Lodge, New York, New York, 1944-1945 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Lodge No. 525, McDowell Lodge, Welch, West Virginia, 1941 (Box 130, Folder 1)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 619 effective Jan. 10, 1944
    - Lodge No. 525, Jefferson Lodge, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1921-1939 (Box 130, Folder 1)
      Consolidated with Lodges Nos. 584 and 923 effective Aug. 7, 1939
  - Sub-Series 235-526. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 526, Princess Lodge, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1939-1959 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 235-527. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 527, Nickel Plate Lodge, Muncie, Indiana, 1922-1956 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 235-528. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 528, Great Falls Lodge, Great Falls, Montana, 1922-1959 (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 235-530. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 530, Hermitage Lodge, Nashville, Tennessee, 1945-1960 (Box 130, Folder 5)
      Consolidated with Lodges 297, 553, 450, and 228 effective Oct. 1, 1960
    - Lodge No. 530, Lakeview Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1922-1945 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 235-531. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 531, Hope Lodge, Huntington, West Virginia, 1946-1962 (Box 130, Folder 6)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 560 effective Jan. 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-533. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 533, Sanford (from Palatka), Florida, 1960 (Box 130, Folder 7)
      Oct. 1, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1523 effective Oct. 1, 1960
    - Lodge No. 533, Quincy Lodge, Quincy, Illinois, 1937-1939 (Box 130, Folder 7)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 439 effective April 5, 1939
  - Sub-Series 235-537. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 537, Cavalier Lodge, Roanoke, Virginia, 1923-1959 (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 235-541. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 541, Mansfield, Ohio, 1921-1923 (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 235-545. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 545, Wayne Lodge, Fort Wayne, Indiana, 1922-1962 (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 235-546. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 546, Sandusky, Ohio, 1923-1962 (Box 130, Folder 11)
      Consolidated with Lodges 502 and 1189 effective Jan. 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-549. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 549, Galewood Lodge, Chicago, Illinois-Expulsion, Harry King, 1947-1953 (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - Lodge No. 549, Galewood Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1950-1959 (Box 130, Folder 13)
      1950-Dec. 31, 1959.
    - Lodge No. 549, Galewood Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1945-1949 (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - Lodge No. 549, Galewood Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1929-1944 (Box 130, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 235-554. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 554, Victory Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri-Warren M. Barnett, 1960-1962 (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - Lodge No. 554, Victory Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1958-1962 (Box 130, Folder 17)
    - Lodge No. 554, Victory Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1953-1957 (Box 130, Folder 18)
      April 1953-Dec. 31, 1957.
    - Lodge No. 554, Victory Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1947-1953 (Box 130, Folder 19)
      1947-March 1953.
    - Lodge No. 554, Victory Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1921-1946 (Box 130, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 235-555. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 555, Brunswick Lodge, Brunswick, Georgia, 1923-1942 (Box 130, Folder 21)
      Disbanded effective Sept. 21, 1942
  - Sub-Series 235-558. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 558, Weston Lodge, Weston, West Virginia, 1922-1957 (Box 130, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 235-559. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 559, Clinchfield Lodge, Johnson City, Tennessee, 1936-1960 (Box 130, Folder 23)
      1936-Dec. 31, 1960. From Erwin, Tennessee
  - Sub-Series 235-566. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 566, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1951 (Box 130, Folder 24)
      Consolidated with Lodges 932 and 948 effective Oct. 22, 1951
    - Lodge No. 566, Anniston Lodge, Anniston, Alabama, 1925-1930 (Box 130, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 235-567. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 567, Monumental Lodge, Baltimore, Maryland-"Monumental Monthly Review", 1924-1927 (Box 130, Folder 25)
      June 1924-June 1927.
    - Lodge No. 567, Monumental Lodge, Baltimore, Maryland, 1921-1952 (Box 130, Folder 26)
      1921-Dec. 31, 1952.
  - Sub-Series 235-568. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 568, Windsor, Ontario, Canada, 1936-1943 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 235-572. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 572, Tri-State Lodge, Elkhart, Indiana, 1937-1958 (Box 131, Folder 2)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 464 effective July 1, 1957
    - Lodge No. 572, Richmond Lodge, Richmond, Virginia, 1921-1923 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 235-581. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 581, Fidelity Lodge, Decatur, Alabama, 1928-1964 (Box 131, Folder 3)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 691 effective July 1, 1964
  - Sub-Series 235-583. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 583, Crampton Lodge, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1922-1963 (Box 131, Folder 4)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 562 effective April 1, 1963
  - Sub-Series 235-584. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 584, Diamond State Lodge, Wilmington, Delaware, 1922-1962 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 235-585. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 585, Waukesha, Wisconsin, 1925 (Box 131, Folder 6)
      Aug. 8, 1925. Disbanded?
  - Sub-Series 235-587. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 587, Quaker City Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1923-1962 (Box 131, Folder 7)
      1923-Dec. 31, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 235-590. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 590, Keystone Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1923-1962 (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 235-591. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 591, Steel City Lodge, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1921-1960 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 235-593. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 593, St. Paul Lodge, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1928-1962 (Box 131, Folder 10)
      1928-Dec. 31, 1962.
    - Lodge No. 593, St. Paul Lodge, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1922-1927 (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 235-594. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 594, Progressive Lodge, Durham, North Carolina, 1924-1960 (Box 131, Folder 12)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 302 effective Oct. 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-595. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 595, Daniel Gusweiler Lodge, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1947-1955 (Box 131, Folder 13)
      July 1947-Dec. 31, 1955. Changed from General Pershing Lodge
    - Lodge No. 595, General Pershing Lodge, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1922-1927 (Box 131, Folder 14)
      1922-June 1927.
  - Sub-Series 235-596. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 596, South Water Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1925-1968 (Box 131, Folder 15)
      Consolidated with Lodges 318, 695, and 774 effective Jan. 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-599. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 599, Ramsey (changed from Hennepin) Lodge, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1921-1964 (Box 131, Folder 16)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 838 effective Jan. 1, 1965
  - Sub-Series 235-602. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 602, Los Angeles Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1921-1960 (Box 131, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 235-603. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 603, Justice Lodge, Pitcairn, Pennsylvania, 1922-1952 (Box 131, Folder 18)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 1282 effective April 1, 1952
  - Sub-Series 235-604. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 604, Harbor Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1923-1956 (Box 131, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 235-606. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 606, Renovo Lodge, Renovo, Pennsylvania, 1921-1922 (Box 131, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 235-607. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 607, Reading Freight Handlers Lodge, Reading, Pennsylvania, 1925-1956 (Box 131, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 235-608. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 608, Pittsburgh Freight Handlers Lodge, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1922-1960 (Box 131, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 235-609. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 609, Columbus Lodge, Columbus, Ohio, 1922-1929 (Box 131, Folder 23)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 610
  - Sub-Series 235-610. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 610, Arch City Lodge, Columbus, Ohio, 1922-1956 (Box 131, Folder 24)
      1922-April 30, 1956.
  - Sub-Series 235-614. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 614, Garfield Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1924-1961 (Box 131, Folder 25)
      1924-Dec. 31, 1961.
  - Sub-Series 235-615. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 615, Missouri Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1922-1957 (Box 132, Folder 1)
      1922-June 31, 1957.
    - Lodge No. 615, Missouri Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri-Appeal in case of Grady Jackson, 1956 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 235-618. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 618, Sante Fe Chicago Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1939-1963 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 235-620. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 620, Garret W. Daly Lodge, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1921-1959 (Box 132, Folder 4)
      1921-Dec. 31, 1959. Changed from Old Glory Lodge
  - Sub-Series 235-624. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 624, Summit Lodge, Akron, Ohio, 1939-1966 (Box 132, Folder 5)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 238 effective April 1, 1966
    - Lodge No. 624, Hawkeye Lodge, Carrol, Iowa, 1921-1929 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 235-626. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 626, Vancouver Lodge, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1947-1950 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 235-630. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 630, Pacific Lodge, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1922-1959 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 235-636. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 636, Entente Lodge, Trenton, Missouri, 1927-1966 (Box 132, Folder 8)
      Consolidated with Lodges 767 and 2024 effective Jan. 1, 1966
  - Sub-Series 235-640. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 640, Penn Harris Lodge, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, 1922-1946 (Box 132, Folder 9)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 421 effective April 1, 1946
  - Sub-Series 235-641. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 641, Ogden Lodge, Ogden, Utah, 1948-1962 (Box 132, Folder 10)
      1948-Dec. 31, 1962.
    - Lodge No. 641, Ogden Lodge, Ogden, Utah, 1923-1948 (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 235-643. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 643, Pere Marquette Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1923-1955 (Box 132, Folder 12)
      Consolidated with Lodges 8 and 523 effective April 1, 1955
  - Sub-Series 235-647. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 647, Chester W. Harrison Lodge, Detroit, Michigan, 1935-1962 (Box 132, Folder 13)
      1935-Dec. 31, 1962. Changed from Cincinnatus Lodge
  - Sub-Series 235-652. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 652, Fort William, Ontario, Canada, 1936-1938 (Box 132, Folder 14)
      Suspended effective Sept. 28, 1938
    - Lodge No. 652, New York, New York, 1939-1942 (Box 132, Folder 15)
      Disbanded effective July 27, 1942
  - Sub-Series 235-653. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 653, Reading General Office Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1921-1959 (Box 132, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 235-655. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 655, Southern Kansas Division Lodge, Chanute, Kansas, 1944-1949 (Box 132, Folder 17)
      Consolidated with Lodges Nos. 174 and 208
    - Lodge No. 655, Fort Wayne, Indiana, 1922 (Box 132, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 235-657. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 657, General Office Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1921-1922 (Box 132, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 235-658. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 658, Elmira Lodge, Elmira, New York, 1921-1957 (Box 132, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 235-659. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 659, Cupples Station Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1936 (Box 132, Folder 20)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 449 in 1936
  - Sub-Series 235-660. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 660, Stevens Point Lodge, Stevens Point, Wisconsin, 1921-1958 (Box 132, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 235-661. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 661, Ferdinand Foch Lodge, Sedalia, Missouri, 1923-1959 (Box 132, Folder 22)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 740 effective Jan. 1, 1959
  - Sub-Series 235-662. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 662, Bridge City Lodge, Logansport, Indiana, 1927 (Box 132, Folder 23)
      1927 July 25. Disbanded
  - Sub-Series 235-665. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 665, Moose Jaw Lodge, Moose Jaw, Saskatchewan, Canada, 1922-1959 (Box 132, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 235-666. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 666, Royal Gorge Lodge, Pueblo, Colorado, 1929-1958 (Box 132, Folder 25)
      1929-Dec. 31, 1958.
  - Sub-Series 235-669. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 669, Chicago, Illinois, 1923-1942 (Box 132, Folder 26)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 1051 effective Nov. 5, 1942
  - Sub-Series 235-670. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 670, Detroit Warehouse Lodge, Detroit, Michigan, 1921-1968 (Box 132, Folder 27)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 38 effective July 1, 1967
  - Sub-Series 235-671. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 671, Glen Miller Lodge, Richmond, Indiana, 1921-1935 (Box 132, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 235-672. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 672, Binghamton Lodge, Binghamton, New York, 1922-1962 (Box 132, Folder 29)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 206 effective Jan. 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-673. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 673, Alliance Lodge, Alliance, Ohio, 1921-1930 (Box 132, Folder 30)
    - Lodge No. 673, Bridge City Lodge, Logansport, Indiana, 1936-1957 (Box 132, Folder 31)
      1936-Dec. 31, 1957.
  - Sub-Series 235-674. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 674, Virginian Lodge, Norfolk, Virginia, 1939-1960 (Box 132, Folder 32)
      Consolidated with Lodges 302, 1090, 1385, and 500 effective Jan. 1, 1960
    - Lodge No. 674, Pacific Coast Lodge, Seattle, Washington, 1932 (Box 132, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 235-675. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 675, Rover Lodge, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1926-1961 (Box 132, Folder 33)
      1926-Dec. 31, 1961. Transferred from Chicago, Illinois effective Sept. 8, 1952
  - Sub-Series 235-679. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 679, Chicago and Northwestern Lodge, Chicago, Illinois-Consolidation Rosters 13 and 17, Appeal A. C. Hartung, 1958-1959 (Box 132, Folder 34)
    - Lodge No. 679, Chicago and Northwestern Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1921-1961 (Box 132, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 235-682. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 682, Helen Hill Lodge, Lancaster, Ohio, 1921-1951 (Box 132, Folder 36)
      Consolidated with various lodges effective Oct. 1, 1951
  - Sub-Series 235-684. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 684, Trailways Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1942-1959 (Box 132, Folder 37)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 602 effective Jan. 1, 1960
    - Lodge No. 684, Stilwell Lodge, Port Arthur, Texas, 1921 (Box 132, Folder 37)
      Feb. 24, 1921. Consolidated with Lodge No. 901 effective Aug. 5, 1942
  - Sub-Series 235-685. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 685, Reservation Bureau, 1945-1959 (Box 133, Folder 1)
      1945-Dec. 31, 1959. Changed from Pullman Lodge, New York, New York
  - Sub-Series 235-686. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 686, Muskagee Lodge, Muskagee, Oklahoma, 1961-1969 (Box 133, Folder 2)
      Jan. 1, 1961-69. Dissolved effective April 1, 1969, members transferred to Lodges 19 and 740
    - Lodge No. 686, Muskagee Lodge, Muskagee, Oklahoma, 1923-1960 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 235-688. Local Lodges